原创翻译  双语字幕
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
很抱歉我不能
I'm so sorry I couldn't
成为神秘符号的守护者  父亲
be the keeper of the Sacred Symbols, Father.
赫隆米尔给了我们托兹沙漠中心的符号
H'ronmeer gave us the symbols in the heart of the desert of T'ozz.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
我可以把它们还回去
I could return them there.
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
这不只是创伤后应激障碍了
This is more than PTSD.
我们必须要告诉莉娜
We have to talk to Lena.
我们伟大国家的核心遭受了超女的袭击
Our great nation was attacked by Supergirl.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我在此颁布戒严令
I am hereby enacting martial law.
超女  如果你正在收看
And, Supergirl, if you are watching,
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
你现在是头号公敌
you are now public enemy number one.
我现在所做的利大于弊
I am doing more harm than good right now.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
有句老话叫什么
What do they say?
笔头强于剑
The pen is mightier than the sword.
总监     你是不是饿得慌
或许比披风还强大
Maybe even mightier than a cape.
寻找莱克·斯卢瑟与真相
滚回去  外星人
Go home, alien!
天已经黑了
It's after dark.
开门  外星人
Open the door, alien!
那是什么
What was that?
超女吗
Supergirl?
你好啊  小伙子们
Howdy, boys.
-你是谁  -我是你最恐怖的噩梦
- Who are you? - I'm your worst nightmare.
做个好梦
Sweet dreams.
离开那里  梦想者
Get out of there, Dreamer.
超查部的车正向你驶去
The DEO van is headed your way
这个地方马上就要满是洛克伍德的人了
and this place is about to be swarming with Lockwood's men.
睡美人
超 女
第四季 第十九集
戒严令只开始了几天
We are only days into martial law
而人们已经开始注意到你了
and already people are catching wind of you.
我们必须讲究策略
We must be strategic.
-布莱尼  你在担心我吗  -是的
- Brainy, are you worried about me? - Yes.
《外星人赦免法》的废除
The repeal of Alien Amnesty
让我们都处于危险之中
has left us all vulnerable.
本·洛克伍德正在围捕那些
Ben Lockwood is out there rounding up aliens
他相信有反人类倾向的外星人
he believes have anti-human leanings.
而面具义警是头号目标
And masked vigilantes are target number one.
总得有人保护无辜群众吧
Well, someone has to protect innocent people.
现在超女在保持低调  我们应该继承衣钵
With Supergirl lying low, we have to pick up the cape.
你也可以变个身
You know, you could always blue-green up
加入我的行动
and join me out there.
没有超女  有63.6%的几率
Without Supergirl, there's a 63.6% chance
我们俩会被抓捕
that you and I will be apprehended.
如果我们不聪明谨慎行事的话
If we are not smart and careful that-- -
不好意思
If you'll excuse me...
你认真的吗
Seriously?
你从一开始就只是全息投影吗
You were a hologram the whole time?
我们得之后再谈了
We'll have to continue this spat later.
等等
Wait!
心跳是186  颅内压为22毫米汞柱
Heartrate is 186. His ICP at 22 mil,
高压160  低压30  还在不断上升
and his BP is 160 over 30 and rising.
心电图不稳
EKG now erratic.
请原谅我指出显而易见的事情
Pardon me for stating the obvious,
但我认为移除手术没起作用
but I do not believe the extraction process is working.
你在抽取血浆  而不是哈伦·艾尔
You're pulling plasma, not Harun-El,
而且你在加剧他的症状
and you're exacerbating his symptoms.
没事的
It's okay.
继续
Keep going.
天啊  好吧  我没事
Oh, God... Okay... I'm fine.
对不起  我以为这会起作用
I'm sorry. I thought this would work.
这项艾美特克科技
I took this AmerTek technology
是我直接从莱克斯牢房拿来的
straight from Lex's cell
而且我完全遵照了伊芙实验室的说明
and I followed the instruction plans from Eve's lab exactly.
出于科研需要  我想问
In the interest of science,
你刚才体验到的是不是超级听力
was that super hearing you just experienced?
现在连超级听力都有了
Super-hearing now, too?
看起来每次恐慌都会激发出新能力
It seems every panic attack is bringing out a new ability.
我会解决的  但我需要更深入地了解它
I will fix this. I just... need to better understand this.
那要花一段时间
That's gonna take time.
-我们得另想策略  -是啊
- We need another strategy. - Yeah.
詹姆斯走运了  我是策略大师
Well, luckily for James, I am adept at strategies.
你听说过思想宫殿吗
Have you ever heard of a mind palace?
詹姆斯
James...
这是你要的黑色预算
Here's the black budget you asked for.
正如说好的  一切都井然有序  光明正大
As discussed, everything is in order and above board.
伊芙
Eve.
该死
Shoot.
最后出现在L公司
莱克斯·卢瑟
偷取莉娜的研究
曼塔罗
伊芙实验室的曼塔罗还活着
逃跑  去哪里了
艾美特克
安斯利成员
谁是总裁
这里的工作人员谁与莱克斯有联系
埃德娜  如果你被抓到篡改外星人档案
Edna, if you get caught changing alien personnel records,
艾美特克可不仅仅会开除你
AmerTek might do more than just fire you.
小心点
Just be careful.
你是在和艾美特克的工作人员谈话吗
Were you just talking to someone that works at AmerTek?
我的姐姐
My sister.
我在写一篇揭露莱克斯·卢瑟的报道
Well, I'm working on an article to expose Lex Luthor
我知道艾美特克也牵涉其中
and I know AmerTek was involved.
你觉得你姐姐会愿意跟我谈谈吗
Do you think your sister would be willing to talk to me?
我不知道
I don't know. It's--
弗兰克林  你昨晚在这里过的夜吗
Franklin, did you sleep here?
洛克伍德和他的人
Lockwood and his men raided
突袭了我家街对面的建筑
the building across the street from mine.
真抱歉
I am so sorry.
我也是
Me too.
但正因如此  我们才要阻止这一切
But that is why this is so important for us to put a stop to.
让你姐姐给我打电话
Have your sister call me?
谢了  弗兰克林
Thanks, Franklin.
卡拉
Kara?
弗兰克林害怕回家
Franklin is afraid to go home.
你不认为  或许
Don't you think that maybe...
你该重新加入超级朋友了吗
it's time for you to rejoin the Super friends?
尼娅  你以为我不想吗
Nia, don't you think I wish I could?
可看看人们都在说些什么
But look what people are saying.
超女狩猎仍在继续
我现在唯一能帮忙做的就是曝光莱克斯
Exposing Lex is the only way I can help right now,
等我曝光他  就能为超女正名
and when I do, it will clear Supergirl's name
我就可以重新和你一起去帮助人们
and I can get back out there with you and help people.
好  你说得对  你继续追查莱克斯
Okay. No, you're right. You stay on Lex.
但我会守卫街头
But I'm gonna watch the streets.
得有人确保洛克伍德晚上安安分分的
Someone needs to make Lockwood go nighty-night-night.
思维宫殿是詹姆斯脑中
A mind palace is a hyper-real
一个超真实的互动空间
interactive space in James' mind.
这个装置接入詹姆斯的颞叶
This device taps into James' temporal lobe,
允许我勾勒出他的记忆
allowing me to map out his memories.
他经历的一切都将是真实的
Everything he experiences will be real and true.
假如詹姆斯能确定并面对他的核心创伤
If James is able to identify and face his core trauma,
他或许能抑制住发作
he may be able to manage the attacks.
我们知道哈伦·艾尔为什么会让发作加剧吗
Do we know why the Harun-El is making the attacks worse?
莉娜的药物旨在攻击疾病
Lena's drug was designed to attack illness.
这次它集中攻击创伤后应激障碍
In this case, it was focused on the PTSD,
加剧了原本普通的恐慌发作
heightening what would normally be just a panic attack.
而由于药物也赋予了你超能力
And since the drug also gives you superpowers,
发作导致了这些能力失控
the attacks were causing the powers to be uncontrollable.
你是说即使我能控制住症状
So, you're saying even if I'm able to manage the symptoms,
也还是会有超能力
I'm still gonna have superpowers?
是的
Yes.
但你能控制它们
But you'll be able to control them.
那我们这就开始吧
Now, shall we jump in?
开始吧
Let's do this.
-快走  -他不是反人类同谋
- Let's go! - He's not a anti-human conspirator.
-快走  -他什么都没做  他是无辜的
- Let's go. - He didn't do anything. He's innocent.
把门打开
Open the door.
求你了  他是个好人
Please. He's a good man.
假如他是人  就不会发生现在这种事了
If he were a man, we wouldn't be in this situation now.
别把事情闹大
Don't make a scene.
你的孩子们刚失去了父亲
Your children, they just lost their father.
我可不想看到他们也失去母亲
I would hate to see them lose their mother, too.
他们看起来和人一样  我
They look so human, I...
有时我会忘记
Sometimes I forget.
是啊  这要艰难得多
Yeah, it's a lot easier
毕竟不是所有外星人后脑都会钻出蛇
when there's a snake coming out of the back of their head.
我们不能把他们当人看  孩子
We can't humanize them, son.
记住  永远不要忘记
So, remember, don't ever mistake them
他们只是蟑螂  仅此而已
for anything but the roaches that they are.
马库斯  你过来一下好吗
Hey, Marcus, you come over here for a second?
做得很好
Excellent work.
我在想  你能不能带上乔治
So, would you... I was thinking maybe you could take George
直到你轮班结束
along for the rest of your shift.
他还在适应我们的工作
He's still gaining a stomach for what we're doing.
很好  我们走
Great. Let's go.
谢谢  祝你今天愉快
Thank you. Have a good one.
我的钱包  别跑  救命
Oh, my purse! Stop! Help!
真不好意思
Oh, I'm so sorry.
我笨手笨脚的  我好内疚
I am such a klutz. I feel so bad.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
卡拉·丹弗斯  我是弗兰克林的姐姐
Kara Danvers? I'm Franklin's sister.
埃德娜
Edna?
阿美特克情况很糟
Things at AmerTek are bad.
真的很糟
Really bad.
我甚至听到流言说  他们下周要在入口处
I even heard a rumor they're installing alien detection devices
安装外星人检测装置
on the entrances next week.
阿美特克在过去18个月里
Has AmerTek done business with Lex Luthor
有没有跟莱克斯或他的同伙有过交易
or any of his associates in the past 18 months?
我是人事部的
I'm in HR.
你能带我去查看那些记录吗
Can you get me access to those records?
我希望这些家伙被拿下
Look, I want these guys taken down.
可他们在围攻外星人
But they are rounding up aliens.
我的行为可能会让家人与朋友陷入险境
And my actions could put my friends and family in danger.
埃德娜  我知道现在事态很吓人
Edna, I know it's scary right now,
但弗兰克林告诉我你一直很勇敢
but Franklin told me how brave you've been.
你把办公室里外星人的个人档案销毁了
Taking the personnel files of the aliens in your office.
正在发生的这些事是错误的
What's happening is wrong.
但我们唯一能阻止它的方法
But the only way we can stop it
就是曝光正在犯下这些罪行的人们
is by exposing the people that are committing these crimes.
你能帮我吗
Can you help me?
谢谢你一直留在这  这意义重大
Thank you for being here. It means a lot.
我非常愿意守在这里
Oh, there's no place I would rather be.
你的核心创伤
There is an 86.7% chance
有86.7%的几率与莱克斯·卢瑟有关
that your core trauma has something to do with Lex Luthor.
我们就从探索那个区域开始
So, we shall start by exploring that region.
都准备好开始了吗
Are we all ready to begin?
很好
Good.
这里是《星球日报》
I'm at the Daily Planet?
欢迎来到第一层
Welcome to level one.
超人是谁
这是我刚遇到超人之后的事
This is right after I met Superman.
莱克斯第一次绑架我
The first time Lex kidnapped me.
不不不  等等  等等
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
这不对劲  这不是那天发生的事
This is... Something wrong. This is not how it happened that day.
这些记忆彼此交织在一起
The memories are folding in on one another.
他们是谁  你们是谁
Who are they? Who are you?
布莱尼  你们那里发生了什么
Brainy, what is going on in there?
那是我
That's me.
发生了什么
What happened?
我见到爸爸了
I saw Dad.
还要多久才能好
How much longer is this gonna take?
快了
Not long.
塞巴斯蒂安·梅莫斯  鲁布尼纳基地
鲁布尼纳的军事基地
A military base in Rubniu?
塞巴斯蒂安·梅莫斯是什么人
Who's Sebastian Melmoth?
我查过所有艾美特克的高管
I researched all the AmerTek executives.
我从来没见过他的名字
I never saw his name.
你在人事部  能把他的工作记录拿给我吗
You're in HR. Could you get me his employment records?
这些服务器需要我的个人密码
Those servers require my personal PIN number.
他们会知道是我干的
They'd know it was me.
有人来了
Someone's coming.
档案室开着灯吗
Is there a light on in the records room?
今天没人要求进入
No one's requested access today.
-我们要躲起来  -是谁在里面
- We have to hide. - Hey, who's in there?
门冻起来了  肯定是高压交流电的问题
The door's frozen shut. Must be an HVAC problem.
我去叫维修工来开门
I'll get maintenance to open the door.
没事了   没事了
It's okay, it's okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
但你不知道
But you don't know what it's like
因为自己的真实身份
to walk around with a target on your back
时刻被人盯着的那种滋味
just because of what you are.
我不能留下记录  我不能这么做
I can't go on the record. I can't do this.
开始哈伦·艾尔抽取实验7.5
Begin Harun-El extraction trial 7.5.
实验对象脉搏为每分钟180次
Object is at 180 BPM,
仪器设置到350兆赫
device is set to 350 megahertz.
标志5  肿瘤正在形成
Mark five. Tumors emerging.
心脏体积扩大到30%
Heart volume expanding to 30%.
艾美特克
天呐  我们好像搞定了
By George, I think we've got it.
我们无意中发现你有严重的创伤  詹姆斯
We just stumbled upon your core trauma, James.
令人惊讶的是  不是莱克斯·卢瑟谋杀未遂
And surprisingly, it isn't a Lex Luthor murder attempt.
而是你父亲的死
It's your father's death.
布莱尼  你说过我在你思维殿堂里看到的事
Brainy, you said that whatever I saw in your mind palace
是基于真实的记忆
was gonna be based on real memories.
我没参加过我们父亲的葬礼
I wasn't at our father's funeral.
你在场
Yes. You were.
毫无疑问
Incontrovertibly.
不  布莱尼  他没去
No, Brainy, he wasn't.
我当时孤单一人
I was alone.
这种事是不会忘记的
That is not something you forget.
设想一下詹姆斯有可能在场
Consider the possibility that James was there,
而你  凯丽  没有看到他
and you, Kelly, did not see him.
我在街对面
I was across the street.
在一间餐厅里
At a diner.
我被锁在洗手间里  没人听到我的声音
I got locked in the bathroom and nobody could hear me.
当经理把门打开的时候
By the time the manager opened up the door,
他的葬礼
his funeral...
他的葬礼已经结束了
His funeral was over.
也许那只是真相的画面
Perhaps that is merely a picture of the truth
印在你脑海里了
that got framed and hung in your mind.
随着时间推移  你自己编造的借口
An excuse you invented that over time,
甚至连你都相信了
even you came to believe.
大脑会搞小动作来进行自我保护
The mind will play tricks to protect itself.
把回忆想象成一幅水彩画
Think of memories like a watercolor.
在你绘画的时候
While you're painting,
颜色相互融合  没有清晰的界限
the colors blend into each other without clear borders
直到它们变得不透明
until they grow opaque.
一旦画干了之后
Once the painting dries,
-画就完成了  -对不起  我要休息一会
- the picture is set. - Yeah, I'm sorry, I need a break.
是因为我的比喻吗
Was it my metaphor?
我知道看到兄弟姐妹痛苦有多难受
Look, I know how hard it is to see a sibling in pain.
但是你  你必须要知道
But you... you have to know
我和布莱尼是不会让詹姆斯有事的
that Brainy and I are not gonna let anything happen to James.
不是因为这个
It's... It's not that.
这些记忆触动了我
The memories are triggering for me.
你是说詹姆斯参加了你父亲的葬礼吗
You mean James at your dad's funeral?
詹姆斯没参加葬礼  艾丽克斯
James wasn't at the funeral, Alex.
我当时八岁
I was eight.
那是我人生中最糟糕的一天
And it was the worst day of my life.
我爸过世了
My dad was dead.
我妈伤心不已  我姑姑不得不扶着她
And my mom was so distraught that my aunts had to hold her up.
我很害怕她也会过世
I was scared that she was gonna die, too.
詹姆斯向我发誓说他会陪着我
James swore to me that he would be by my side.
一切都会好起来的
That everything was gonna be okay
因为我们会一起面对
because we were gonna face it together.
葬礼前他就不见了
He disappeared before the service.
我坐在那里
And I sat there,
孤单一人
alone,
泪流满面
tears streaming down my face,
看着大门  等着我哥哥
staring at the door, waiting for my big brother
走进来  让一切...
to walk in and make everything...
让一切好起来
Make everything okay.
他却没出现
He never showed up.
他当时在哪
Where was he?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道他当时到底在哪
I don't know where he really was.
我明白  他当时也是孩子
And, look, I get it. He was a kid, too.
但我实在不想重温那一天
But it is not a day that I am aching to relive.
我明白
I understand.
我和你非常像
You know, you and I are a lot alike.
我们真的很会照顾其他人
We're really good at taking care of other people
但却很不会照顾自己
but not so good at taking care of ourselves.
你不必这么做
You don't have to do this.
我可以替你留在詹姆斯身边
Yeah, I can stay by James' side for you.
我
I, um...
其实  我应该可以做到
I actually... I think I can do it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
塞巴斯蒂安·梅莫斯
Sebastian Melmoth.
你是谁
Who are you?
你为什么十月份
Why were you buying property
会在根本不存在的鲁布尼纳买房子呢
in the non-existent land of Rubniu in October?
鲁布尼纳
塞巴斯蒂安·梅莫斯
10月10日军事基地
他们有多少卫星办公室
莱克斯的藏身之处呢
提款58.7亿美元
塞巴斯蒂安·梅莫斯
L公司账户转账记录
莉娜
Lena.
有人吗
Hello?
卡拉
Kara?
真是惊喜
What a surprise.
是啊  你的新助理让我进来的
Yeah, your new assistant let me in.
她看起来人不错
She seems nice.
希望她不会从背后捅我一刀
Let's hope she doesn't stab me in the back.
莉娜  伊芙之前对你做的事  我很抱歉
Lena, I'm so sorry about what Eve did to you.
谢谢
Thanks.
我来其实就是为了这件事
It's actually why I'm here. Uh...
我在写一篇关于莱克斯的报道
I'm writing an article about Lex.
我想曝光他
I wanna expose him.
我想让他下台  从而结束这一切
I want to take him down and put an end to all of this.
曝光莱克斯
An expose on Lex.
这个目标很远大
That's quite an Everest.
其实我是想问你一个问题
Uh, there was actually something I was hoping you could answer.
L公司与阿美特克公司合作过吗
Has L-Corp done business with AmerTek?
比如一个军事项目
Maybe on a military project?
当然没有
No, of course not.
很抱歉我现在不能帮你  我...
Look, I'm sorry I can't help you with this right now. I'm...
我想救詹姆斯
I'm trying to help James.
艾丽克斯来了
You know, Alex is here.
你一直没来看我
You haven't been around.
但超女在陪着我
Supergirl's been there for me.
她对我的姓氏有偏见  却还是陪着我
Person who judges me on the very premise of my last name
而我最好的朋友却没有
but my best friend hasn't.
莉娜  我
Lena, I'm...
很抱歉  我...
I'm sorry. I was...
我想逮到莱克斯
I was trying to catch Lex.
是为了你  我是为了你才这样做
For you. That's why I'm doing this.
我当然在乎你的感受
Of course I care about how you feel.
但是你更在乎的是
You just care about me a little less
我能否做你报道的线人
than you do as a source for your story.
不  不是这样的  我...
No, no, it's not like that. I...
我很希望能跟你解释  但是
I wish I could explain, but...
我还是走吧
But maybe it's better if I just go.
快进去  免得被别人看到
In there, before someone sees.
你们该上床睡觉了吧
Isn't it past your bedtime?
这是怎么回事
What's going on here?
阿尔让我们把酒吧作为外星人避难所
Al's letting us use the bar as an alien refuge.
我不知道怎么铺床
I don't know how to make my bed.
你能帮帮我吗
Can you help me, please?
我们是外星事务部  你们因违法而被拘捕了
Alien Affairs. You're all in violation and under arrest.
什么叫被拘捕了
What do you mean, "Under arrest"?
我们根本没做错事
We haven't done nothing wrong.
根据戒严令  外星人宵禁后不许聚集
Under martial law, aliens cannot gather after curfew.
把他们带到车上
Get them to the van.
你得先经历这个幻境
You're gonna have to go through this reverie first.
随你吧
Have it your way.
快走
Get out of here.
抓住他们
Get 'em!
我去抓那个孩子
I got the kid.
-查理  -乔治
- Charlie? - George.
请别抓我
Please don't take me in.
你是外星人吗  你为什么没告诉我
You're an alien? Why didn't you tell me?
你觉得呢
Why do you think?
撤退
Fall back!
这下安全了
You're safe now.
安全
Safe?
他们今天没抓到我们
They didn't get us today,
但是还会回来的
but they'll be back.
我们是外星人
We're aliens.
没有安全的地方了
Nowhere is safe.
我很熟悉你这个皱眉的表情
I know that crease in your brow.
亲爱的  告诉我怎么了
Sweetie, tell me what's wrong.
只是...
It... It's just...
你有没有怀疑过...
Do you ever wonder about, um... Like...
爸爸的政策
Dad's policies?
也许  我们的做法是错的
You know, like, maybe we're doing this wrong?
当然没有  乔治
Of course not, George.
你爸正在拯救这个国家
Your dad is saving this country.
对酒吧的搜查不是很顺利
And the raid at the bar didn't go as planned,
但你帮忙把那些蟑螂赶出了洞穴
but you helped smoke those roaches out of their hole
你爸爸很为你骄傲
and your father is so proud of you.
尼娅
Nia...
怎么了
What is it?
阿尔的地下酒吧
Al's dive bar.
他把那里作为了外星人避难所
He's been using it as a shelter for aliens
洛克伍德的手下突袭了那里
and Lockwood's goons just crashed it.
我阻止了他们  但是
I stopped them. But...
那里的人还是感到很无助
The people there still felt so hopeless.
我想做更多事来帮助他们  但是
And I wanna do more to help them. I just
我不知道我还能做什么
don't know what else I can do.
我完全能理解你的感受
I know exactly how you feel.
我太顾及眼前  反而让事情恶化了
I've been so myopic I think I've made things worse.
我让弗兰克林的姐姐更害怕了
I made Franklin's sister more afraid.
更不用说
Not to mention
我对莉娜特别不够朋友
I've been a terrible friend to Lena.
你怎么不够朋友了
Uh-- How have you been a terrible friend?
自从莱克斯逃跑  你就一直被束缚着
You've been lockstep ever since Lex escaped.
那是超女
That was Supergirl.
好吧
Right.
天哪  外面情况真糟糕
God, it just sucks out there.
真希望能够给每个外星人都写一篇
I wish we could do your Aliens of National City story
《纳欣诺市的外星人们》
with every alien.
这样人类就会知道
Then the humans would know
他们不需要害怕外星人
that they don't need to be afraid of them.
也许他们只是需要认识一个外星人
Maybe they just need to get to know one alien.
什么意思
How do you mean?
尼娅  尼娅
Nia... Nia!
我们一直专注于打斗和报道
You and I have been so focused on fighting and reporting,
或许  或许我们
that maybe... maybe we
忘记了身为英雄最重要的任务
forgot the most important part of being a hero
就是给人希望
is inspiring hope.
所以超女要回归了吗
So, Supergirl's coming back?
人们现在不需要超女站出来说话
The world doesn't need to hear from Supergirl right now.
他们需要一个英雄
They need a hero who can speak
可以直言社会矛盾
to the conflict society is struggling with.
这个人要同时是外星人和地球人
Someone who is both alien and human.
并且能使双方团结一心
Someone who can bring them together.
-那要怎么做  -我想采访你
- How? - I wanna interview you.
独家采访
An exclusive.
我想向世人介绍
I want to introduce the world
梦想者
to Dreamer.
我知道这对你是很大的挑战  詹姆斯
I know this is challenging, James,
但我会一直陪着你
but I'll be with you every step of the way.
-这是葬礼那天  -你好像来早了
- It's the day of the funeral. - Looks like you're early.
我还记得当时穿的这套衣服
I remember wearing that suit.
我爱你  爸爸
I love you, Dad.
我保证
I promise
我一定会尽我所能
I will spend my life
为你争光
making you proud.
你不能进来
You can't be in here.
葬礼还没开始
The funeral hasn't started yet.
他在那里
There he is.
我们等你很久了  乖小孩
We've been waiting for you, daddy's boy.
我记得他们  比利·纽和布兰登·帕尔默
I remember them. Billy New and Brandon Palmer.
他们嘲笑我  抢我午饭钱
They taunted me, took my lunch money.
我爸爸是军人  放尊重一点
My dad was a soldier. Have some respect.
给他看看什么叫尊重
Let's say we show him some respect.
放开我
Let me go!
不要  不要
Don't do it. Don't do this.
他心率过快了
His vitals are spiking.
努力冲破回忆
Push through the memory.
我的连接断了  没法跟他联系
My connection's lost. I can't reach him.
凯莉
Kelly,
恐怕詹姆斯陷入了小时候的记忆
I fear James' mind has merged with his younger self.
你当时在那里  你可以跟他联系
You were there. You could tether him.
你愿意进去吗
Will you go in?
不  不不不  我不行
No. No, no, no. I can't.
他需要人指引  他会认出你是他妹妹
He needs guidance. He will recognize you as his young sister.
不行  布莱尼  这个要求太过分
No, Brainy, it's too much to ask of her.
肯定还有别的办法
There has to be another way.
让我去吧
I'll do it.
詹姆斯  你能让我进去吗
James, please, can you let me in?
-詹姆斯  -凯莉  我听见你的声音了
- James? - Kelly, I can hear you.
你把我带出去  我不要再看了
You gotta get me out of here. I can't see this.
我就在这
I'm here.
詹姆斯  我在这陪你
James, I'm here with you.
等等  那是你吗
Wait, that's you?
你不是在餐馆吗
You weren't at the diner?
你被困在这里了
You were trapped down here?
那些男生干的吗
Those boys did this to you?
詹姆斯
James?
詹姆斯  你在哪
James, where are you?
天啊  是我的声音
Oh, my God, that's my voice.
我在这里  凯莉  救命
Down here, Kelly. Help!
我在找你
I was looking for you.
你爸爸死了救不了你  你妹妹就能行吗
Dead daddy can't save you. You think your baby sister can?
可怜虫
Pathetic loser.
我一定是把这段羞耻的记忆
I must have pushed the shame of this
埋得太深
and the memory so far down,
就记不起来
I forgot.
餐馆的故事我说了太多遍  自己都信了
I've told that diner story so many times, I believe it.
我希望我在那里  凯莉
I wanted to be there, Kelly.
我希望我...
I wanted to be...
对不起
I'm so sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
你可以改变这一切
You can change this narrative.
反击
Fight back.
去吧
Come on.
詹姆斯  你做到了
James, you did it.
你肯定没问题
You're gonna be great.
准备好了吗
You ready?
准备好了
As I'll ever be.
好
Okay.
我还没提取出来  布莱尼
I haven't figured out the extraction yet, Brainy.
我就是为这个来的
That's why I came up.
可以解除紧急状态了
Urgency is no longer required.
詹姆斯顺利完成了思维殿堂
James has successfully completed his mind palace.
他打开了创伤的记忆
With his trauma unblocked,
看来哈伦·艾尔在他体内得到了控制
the Harun-El seems to have stopped attacking his PTSD
不再引发创伤后应激障碍
and is regulated throughout his body.
使用你的药后  他的长期预后
His long-term prognosis with your drug in his system
会很好
is good.
晚上好
Good evening.
我是凯特科媒体的卡拉·丹弗斯
This is Kara Danvers with CatCo Media
这是一次全球独家采访
and this is a worldwide exclusive.
我身边的这位是一个不为人知的战斗英雄
I'm here with the hero who has been fighting in the shadows.
她就是梦想者
This is Dreamer.
第一个问题
My first question...
你是谁
Who are you?
我是梦想者
I'm Dreamer
我妈妈是纳尔托尔后裔
and I am a descendant of a daughter of Naltor.
你什么时候从纳尔托尔过来的
When did you come here from Naltor?
并没有
I didn't.
我就出生在美国
I was born here in America.
-我在这长大  -把它关掉
- I grew up... - Shut this off.
关不掉  有人黑进了系统
We can't. Someone hacked the system.
人类和外星人和谐相处
...humans and aliens lived together in harmony.
我母亲是纳尔托尔人  但我父亲是人类
My mother was Naltorian, but my father was a human.
所以你既是人类也是外星人
So you are both human and alien.
是的
Yes.
我父母相信人类和外星人可以共存
My parents believed that humans and aliens could co-exist.
我就是活生生的证据
And I'm living proof of that.
但长大并不容易
But growing up wasn't easy.
我还是个女变性人
I am also a trans woman.
丹弗斯女士  我与众不同  但每个人都这样
I'm different, Miss Danvers, but so is everybody.
我不知道这什么时候成了一件坏事
And I don't know when that became such a bad thing.
我们能给彼此的最好礼物
The greatest gift we can give each other
就是真实的自我并分享这一自我
is our authentic selves and sharing that.
分享我们的真实会让我们变得强大
Sharing our truth is what will make us strong.
所以这就是我
So, here I am.
既是人类也是外星人
I am both human and alien.
同时还是变性人
And I am a trans woman.
苏打饼夹烤棉花糖是我最喜欢的甜点
S'mores are my favorite dessert.
但我总是选咸的而不是甜的
But I will always choose salty over sweet.
我十五岁在踢球的时候摔断了鼻子
I broke my nose when I was 15 during a game of kickball.
我母亲是我的心肝
My mother was my heart.
自从我失去她以后
And since I lost her,
感觉就像我的一部分不见了
it's felt like a piece of me is missing.
但我父亲是我的支柱
But my father is my spine.
我是个格兰芬多
I'm a Gryffindor.
我的守护神是一只花斑灰公马
Uh, my patronus is a Dapple Grey Stallion.
MBTI人格16型之一
人格是INFP型
I am an INFP.
一名米兰达
Uh, a Miranda.
支持史塔克家族
House Stark.
我喜欢星期四  喜欢四月
I love Thursdays and April.
还有想得太多的书呆子
And nerdy boys who think too much.
我为我的一切感到骄傲
And I am proud of all that I am.
你就该这样
You should be.
爱是什么感觉
What does love feel like?
既然这个世界知道你是外星人了
Are you afraid of how the world will react to you
你会害怕他们对你的反应吗
now that they know you're an alien?
当然
Of course.
但你还知道吗  恐惧糟透了
But, you know what else? Fear sucks.
那样糟透了
It sucks.
我实在厌倦了感到绝望
And I am so sick of feeling hopeless.
黎明不会自己到来  我们必须主动追求
Dawn doesn't come unless we want it to.
但我们不必等待新时代的到来
But we don't have to wait for a new day.
我们就是新时代
We are the new day.
你妈妈会为你骄傲的
Your mother would be so proud of you.
我的...
Oh, my...
你哭了
You're leaking.
我一直觉得自己坚强又勇敢  但...
I always considered myself strong, brave. But...
像那样分享自己  我...
To share yourself like that, I...
如果我理解对了梦想者所言
If I am understanding Dreamer's words correctly,
那我们都不应该害怕自己是谁
none of us should be afraid of who we are.
也不应该害怕分享这一点
Nor should we fear sharing that.
我现在感觉整个人都瘫痪了  因为我不能...
I feel so paralyzed right now because I'm not able to. I'm...
不能前进了
Not able to move forward.
我找不到莱克斯  我救不了詹姆斯
I can't find Lex. I can't fix James.
我理解
I understand
你这一生中
that you have been betrayed
被很多人背叛过  莉娜
by many people in your life, Lena.
我也知道那种感觉
I know that feeling, too.
但如果你想被信任和接受
But if you want to be trusted and accepted,
那你也必须去信任
then you must also trust.
这会有风险
It will be risky.
但我可以说  如果你关上所有的门
But I can tell you that if you close all doors,
你会有99.9%的概率悲伤
you will have a 99.9% chance of sorrow.
我要抓住这个梦想者  立刻
I want this Dreamer detained. Now.
行动
Let's go.
洛克伍德去了凯特科
我联系不到卡拉
I can't get a hold of Kara.
洛克伍德正赶去凯特科
Lockwood is heading to CatCo.
我要把卡拉和梦想者带走
I gotta get her and Dreamer out of there.
等等  你如果阻止洛克伍德
Wait, you're gonna be
会上军事法庭的
court-martialed if you try to stop Lockwood.
只要他们看不见我们  就抓不到我们
They cannot catch us if they cannot see us.
下次再说吧
So, tell me later.
-好  -干得好  各位
- Okay... - Great job, guys.
-谢谢  -谢谢  弗兰克林
- Thanks. - Thanks, Franklin.
外星事务部  趴下
Alien Affairs! On the ground!
不许动
Don't you move!
梦想者  你被捕了
Dreamer, you are under arrest
因为使用非法反动节目来煽动暴力
for using an illegal seditious broadcast to incite violence.
你才是唯一煽动暴力的人
You're the only one inciting violence.
我们手无寸铁
We're unarmed.
那就简单了
This will be easy, then.
准备好  布莱尼
Ready, Brainy.
她在哪里  找到她然后拘留她
Where is she? Find her and detain her.
你来了啊
You're here.
正如一位聪明女人所说
As a wise woman once said,
"恐惧糟透了"
"Fear sucks."
所以我们来让恐惧见鬼去吧
So let's kick fear's ass.
弗兰克林  你救了我
Franklin, you saved me!
-是吗  -是啊  快找掩护
- I did? - Yeah. Let's take cover.
-好的  可以  -好的
- Yeah. Okay. - Yeah.
我们应该离开这里  被抓也糟透了
We should get out of here. Getting caught also sucks.
梦想者
Dreamer!
你和我一起走吧
You're coming with me.
离开凯特科
Get out of CatCo.
快
Now.
外星人不走我就不走
Not without the alien.
什么外星人
What alien?
我只看到记者
All I see are journalists
在行使他们的言论自由权
exercising their right to freedom of speech
履行她们维护新闻自由的职责
and doing their duty to uphold freedom of press.
所以  除非你是要重写宪法
So, unless you're gonna rewrite the Constitution,
不然给我滚
get out now!
我不知道你是怎么了
I don't know what happened to you
你是怎么办到这一切的
or how you did this.
但我会查清楚
But I'll find out.
我们走
Come on!
我还会找到
Oh, and I will find
这个梦想者
this Dreamer.
卡拉
Kara?
-埃德娜  -昨晚我看了梦想者的节目
- Edna? - I saw the Dreamer broadcast last night.
很鼓舞人心
It was inspiring.
我想你是对的
I realized you were right.
阻止这一切的唯一方法就是揭露这些人
The only way we can stop any of this is by exposing these people.
我有东西要给你
I have something for you.
或许这些会有所帮助
I thought maybe these could help.
这些是那个军事基地的收购文件
These are the acquisition papers for that military base.
但他们会知道是你泄露的
But they'll know it was you.
你的工作怎么办
What about your job?
我不在乎
I don't care.
事实上  如果你需要一个人揭发艾美特克
In fact, if you need an AmerTek whistle-blower,
我愿意公开发言
I'm willing to go on the record.
这
This...
真是太勇敢了
is very brave of you.
你准备好了吗  姐姐
You ready, sis?
谢谢你  埃德娜
Thank you, Edna.
真的
Truly.
对不起我对你如此无礼
I'm sorry I was so short with you.
你只是想做好你的工作
You were just trying to do your job.
维持友谊是最重要的工作
Friendship is the most important job
我之前太专注于我的文章
and I was so focused on my article,
忘了真正重要的东西
I forgot what really matters.
不  卡拉
No, Kara.
其实
The truth is,
就算莱克斯逃跑时你就在我身旁
even if you'd been standing right next to me when Lex escaped
我也会把你支走
I really wouldn't have let you be there for me.
什么意思  为什么
What do you mean? Why?
因为我才是那个有所隐瞒的人
Because I'm the one that's keeping secrets.
伊芙不是唯一帮莱克斯的人  我
Eve wasn't the only one working with Lex. I...
我也助了他一臂之力
I was working with him, too.
他四个月前他就联系了我
He contacted me four months ago.
他知道我有哈伦·艾尔
He knew I had the Harun-El.
他得了癌症  担心会死
He had cancer and he was afraid to die.
他是我的哥哥
He's my brother.
我心里清楚他在操纵我
And in my heart, I knew he was manipulating me
但我相信他
but I believed him
然后我帮了他  他背叛了我
and I helped him and he betrayed me.
我太软弱  我永远不会原谅自己
And I was weak and I will never forgive myself for that.
你对我肯定有看法  卡拉  我不怪你
I can only imagine what you think of me, Kara. I don't blame you.
不  不
No, no.
你并不软弱
You are not weak.
你是个聪明
You are a brilliant,
善良  美丽的人
kind-hearted, beautiful soul.
你哥哥向你求助
Your brother asked you for help
在生死关头  你帮助了家人
and in life and death situations, you help family.
没人能因此批评你
No one can judge you for that.
我很遗憾你觉得不能告诉我这件事
I'm so sorry you felt like you couldn't tell me.
我很遗憾
I am so sorry.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我真的想帮你调查莱克斯
I really wanna help you with your investigation with Lex.
查理  如果你需要朋友  我就在这里  乔治
塞巴斯蒂安·梅莫斯在十月十日
So, Sebastian Melmoth withdrew $5.8 billion
从L公司取出58亿美元
from L-Corp on October 10th.
当天  艾美特克斥资58亿美元
The same day AmerTek paid $5.8 billion
在鲁布尼纳买了一个导弹基地
for a missile base in Rubniu.
偶然吗
Coincidence?
不  我不相信偶然
No, I don't believe in them.
多半是神秘人拿了他在L公司取的钱
More likely, our mystery man took the money he withdrew from L-Corp
再用艾美特克当幌子买下了导弹基地
and paid for the missile base using AmerTek as a smokescreen.
塞巴斯蒂安·梅莫斯是谁  鲁布尼纳在哪
So, who is Sebastian Melmoth and where the hell is Rubniu?
那个爱读经典的混蛋
That nostalgic bastard.
莱克斯13岁读完了奥斯卡·王尔德的作品
When Lex was 13, he read the entire works of Oscar Wilde
他好几周都让我们叫他奥斯卡·王尔德的笔名
and for weeks, he had us call him by Oscar Wilde's pseudonym,
塞巴斯蒂安·梅莫斯
Sebastian Melmoth.
所以是莱克斯·卢瑟买了导弹基地吗
Are we saying that Lex Luthor bought a missile base?
不  不在鲁布尼纳
No, but not in Rubniu.
莱克斯喜欢密码  塞巴斯蒂安也喜欢密码
Lex loves codes, so Sebastian loves codes.
这是双排式中断密钥密码  莱克斯的最爱
It's a double-breasted interrupted key cipher. It's Lex's favorite.
卡兹尼亚
看来我们得去卡兹尼亚
Guess we're going to Kaznia.
不
No.
不  不
No. No.
莉迪娅
Lydia!
不不不  亲爱的
No. No. No. Sweetheart...
不  不
No. No.
不
No!
托兹沙漠
父亲
Father.
做得好  儿子
You have done well, my son.
回家吧
Go home now.
和家人团聚
Join your family.